https://accfoundation.org/privacy-policy/

Affiliated Ministries
ACC Mission Board of Canada
Life Without Limbs
PAZ
UBY (Upward Bound Youth)
Zambia School Sponsorships
What is Realm?
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy describes how Apostolic Christian Church Foundation, Inc. “ACCF” collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: http://accfoundation.org. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.
Information Collection and Use
Emails and Web Forms
From time to time we may collect information from users of our site.  Personal information that you provide by email or web forms will be used only for such purposes as are described at the point of collection (for example on a web form), such as to send information to you or respond to your questions or comments. If you provide contact information, ACCF staff or its contractors may contact you to clarify your comment or question, or to learn about your level of interest in, or satisfaction with our services. We do not share or sell any personal information to third parties except as described in this privacy policy.
The ACCF will provide you with a notification via prominent notice on our website for 30 days of any such change in the control of your personal information.
Blog
Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at YourACCF@gmail.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
Service Providers (including Donations)
We use other third parties to process any and all online donations received (please see the link to ACS Technologies https://www.acstechnologies.com/company/privacy-policy).  These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for promotional purposes.
Information Collected and Stored Automatically
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through our website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically using cookies and log files. We use this information to help make our site more useful to visitors, to learn about the number of visitors to our site, and the types of technology they use.
Log Files
As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base. We do not link this automatically collected data to personal information.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
ACCF uses cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.
We partner with third parties to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out here (or if located in the European Union, here.) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.
Communications From ACCF
Customer Service
We will communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request or in which you express interest. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.
Opt-out of Special Offers and Updates
We may occasionally send you information on services and promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. If you no longer wish to receive our promotional email communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each newsletter, by emailing us at YourACCF@gmail.com.
Updating Personal Information
Upon request ACCF will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. To request this information, please contact us by phone or postal mail at the contact information listed at the end of this policy. We will respond to these requests within a reasonable timeframe.
If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete your information by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed at the end of this policy. We will respond to your request within 30 days.
ACCF has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal information it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to YourACCF@gmail.com. If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.
Links To Other Sites
Our policy discloses the privacy practices for the ACCF website. However, we do provide links to other websites. When you leave http://accfoundation.org you will go to sites outside of our control. These external sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. The privacy policies and procedures described here for ACCF do not apply to any external links. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of any site you link to from ours, especially if you share any personal information. Be informed. You are the person best qualified to protect your own privacy.
Data Retention
We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you services. If you wish to request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at YourACCF@gmail.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information, as well as personal information we process as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at YourACCF@gmail.com.
Changes In This Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate, to inform you of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we change how we use your personal information we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.
Contact Us
Feel free to contact us regarding this privacy policy at YourACCF@gmail.com, by telephone at 330.264.5011, or by postal mail at Apostolic Christian Church Foundation, Inc., PO Box 72, Wooster, Ohio 44691.
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
© Copyright Grand Portfolio Theme Demo - Theme by ThemeGoods
Continue to Payment
Please continue to your payment here.
CLOSE
Contact Us
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Subject
Your Message
CLOSE
Order Complete
If you are buying more than one book, please add up the total price and put in the donation amount.
Junior Hymnal – $12 each
Zion’s Harp Piano Hymnal – $30 each
Please continue to your payment here.
CLOSE
Order Complete
Please continue to your payment here.
CLOSE
Order Complete
Please continue to your payment here.
CLOSE
Order Complete
Please continue to your payment here.
CLOSE
Order Complete
Please continue to payment here.
CLOSE
Continue to Payment
Please continue to your payment here.
CLOSE
